Alvieto Haykal

Surabaya, Indonesia | haykalcs@gmail.com | (62) 822-3489-7335 linkedin.com/in/alvietomhf | alvietomhf.github.io

Backend Developer

First of all, my name is Alvieto Haykal. I love coding and am interested in solving problems while coding. A skilled, competent, and diligent individual, specializing in the backend web development (Laravel - NodeJS/Express/Nest). For the last 2 years, I have been developing applications using PHP, JavaScript, and TypeScript programming languages. At this time I am working as a freelancer making website projects ordered by individuals or institutions. I've hands on in all stages of the programming cycle, from planning to development and deployment. No two days are the same for me; my tasks may involve analyzing algorithms, altering code, fixing bugs, brainstorming ideas for integrating new systems.

Experience

Freelancer, (Sep 2020 - present)

• Makes website projects ordered by individuals or institution

Backend Developer, Runshop (Aug 2021 - Jan 2022)

- Develop multiple modules
- Add bank mutation checker
- Integration with payment gateway
- Integration with notification service

Backend Developer, PT Kipa Teknologi Indonesia (Jan 2021 – Feb 2021) Internship

Develop a project called "Sadean" including:

- Authentication module using JWT
- Customer module
- Product module
- Utility for sending email and firebase push notification

Skills

- Laravel (Expert)
- NestJS (Intermediate)
- NodeJS/Express (Intermediate)
- Docker (Intermediate)

- PHP, JavaScript (Expert)
- HTML, CSS (Expert)
- GitHub Actions/Gitlab CI (Intermediate)
- MySQL, PostgreSQL (Intermediate)

Certifications

Backend Developer Expert (Dicoding Indonesia, 2021)

Education

- Universitas Negeri Surabaya, Teknik Informatika (2018 2022)
- SMA A. Wahid Hasyim Tebuireng Jombang (2015 2018)

Languages

- English Fluent
- Bahasa Indonesia Native